wasn't that fun!
So fun!
What will we do!
it was sparkling
It was!
Cute!
(That's great)
What do ya mean
it's here at last, the finals are tomorrow
do you think we can win
I don't know, but surely it will be a good thing
because we practiced so hard for it
if we win, we'll get the title!
we definitely will
The title goes to Fujigawaka High School dance club
With only 4 members they won the title!
Hey hey hey
I wonder if passion will come
It'll totally happen
If worst comes to worst we'll try our best
yeah
Hey, what do you think Kanako?
Can we win the competition?
What's up, you're being strange
Are you becoming even more crazy?
No
I'm trying to digest it all
You'll eat alright
Not like that!
What do you mean then?
If I were to rank it
This might be the most fun time of my life
As time stands still
I'll eat through it!!!
well..
what was that?
That's not like you
you made me laugh
You're overexaggerating it
No I'm not!
because...
Tommorrow we'll be dancing in front of everyone!
Along with my best friends
The best day is happening tommorrow!
I don't know whether we'll come 1st, 2nd or last
Because I don't know, anything could happen
And it all happens tommorrow
Hey!
is there anything more fun than this?
I don't think there is
Nothing?!
This is definitely the funnest part of my life
Thinking about it
What Kanako said was great
Right!
Do you wanna dance?
And hold my hand
Tell me~
Baby
I'm
Your
Lover
Man
no no no no
What was that?!
Kanako's trying her best
She tried
Right!
Let's practice
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance?
Do you, do you, do you, do you
Do you wanna dance
Oh! Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance?
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance?
Do you, do you, do you, do you
Do you wanna dance
Oh! Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you
Do you wanna dance
Today at 5:20
goniojigoda
year 2 Fujigawaka High School
Takasawa Reni
Tamaki Shiori
Sasano Ayaka
Senda Kanako
The police reported that as a result of dangerous driving
The 4 of them were always
Subbed by Whitbyfish & Retronofu
Ogyaaa
(baby cry)
Pushed out We Are Born
Adjust to the sourroundings
Jumping out and breathing is a must
Start playing an instrument and shout
Happy Birthday, the birthday of your life
Hey boy, this world is heartless
Hey girl, it's a battle of isolation
It's a survival game without any restarts
Beep Beep! Cry all you want
There's no use reaching out desperately
Living easily is against the rules
where's my relief shelter?
I want to keep living a cosy life
I realize I can't go back and panic
We're just frail beings
Ahead the path becomes a wasteland of creatures and ambition
Hug me, Mother!
We are born now, we always have
tears in our eyes
We search this new world for a reason to live
Born now, we have nothing to lose
There's nothing to fear
Even so, powerlessly and ironically, We are born!
A fanfare emerges, fever and dance
It's not a disco, it's discommunication
I want to tell you but I don't know language
Speak, babel comes later, Catch up
The origin of humanity
I'm a baby, I'm a baby, I'm just a baby
No matter how great they were
Yes, yes, yes, yes I was
Life will continue on
Fear & fearless it's endless
From the moment they awaken
Like a bee to a tearful face
No voice, where we were born
No choice, who we'll meet
In the end, we don't get to decide
We still don't know who we are
Baby, to a cutie like you
We have to search for an identity
Baby, Let's give you a name
An unlucky rollercoaster of fate
It's too late to get off!
We are born now, we always have
tears in our eyes
We can't stop ourselves from stepping into the new world
Born now, over and over we're hurt and betrayed
But don't lose hope
Like love, it's ironic, We are born!
In the darkness, in the distance we found
(A shining light)
Yearning for it
We've begun to crawl out of our comfortable world
Along a dark, narrow path
Onwards, onwards
All alone
Onto the next world
We are born now, we always have
tears in our eyes
We search this new world for a reason to live
Born now, we have nothing to lose
There's nothing to fear
Born now, Born now
in order to be born again
forget your fears, raise your head, let's go
Even so, powerlessly and ironically, We are born!
Reni?
Shiori?
Ayaka?
Where did everyone go?
Thinking about it
Where am I?!
Senda~
Kanako-san
Yes...
Stats: born July 12th, 2000
part of the Fujigawaka High School dance club
Last year's grades were:
English - F
Science - F
Math - F
Physical Education - A*
Why are you saying that?
Are you a teacher giving guidence?
I'm the butler, Sakagami
and this is the angel in charge
Mi~Nya
She may look like a normal old person
she smells too much like an old woman
an old woman?
In the past she was terribly cute
Sorry but ill-tempered
Anyone's ok, but do you have a map
I lost my way
but firstly
What is this place?
You don't know?
This cloudy place...
Beppu? (Hot spring city)
Are you an idiot?
It's heaven
HEAVEN?!
Did I die or something?
You didn't notice?
You were in a big accident
I don't know!
I was immersed in dancing
♪So you're an idiot♪
Anyway, let me meet Reni, Shiori and Ayaka
You don't get it
You won't meet again
Why?
already,
You've been reborn
HUH?!
What are you saying, I don't understand
Fine, I'll tell you
I'll tell you, the secret of this world
Over there there are inifite parallel worlds
You're other life
has been reborn it really has
but the past you is not the future you
On the other side of the wall is a parallel world
The next you has been born
So the others are there too?
Yes
They're in a class in another city?
Do they have different names?
Yes
Then let me meet them
NO!
Why?
I'll tell you the secret of this world
The you from the past
no one knows anymore
You're lying
There's no way Reni, Shiroi and Ayaka would ever forget about me
I know that for sure, let me see them
No!
I'll tell you the secret of this world
I'll decide where you're reborn
I'll decide with this gachapon
the place you will go to, the gachapon knows
What are you saying?
I'll tell you the secret of this world
This can cross all the barriers
It can take you to any kind of world
The other side of the wall between worlds
As long as you have this, you can go there
What are you doing!
Don't come any closer
or I'll break it
Stop this! Don't break something brand new, It'll be expensive to replace it
I will dance
Along with Reni, Shiori and Ayaka
I'll make everyone smile with my dance
To me there's no other world
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you
Do you wanna dance
Oh! Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you
Do you wanna dance
Oh! Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you
Do you wanna dance
I'm going now!
Hey you guys, go stop her
Ok
Just leave her be
Let her do as she likes
Minya-sama
Let's have a little more fun with this
You going? You staying?
You should go
Tell me whether you want to say it or not
Front or back, it's an endless question
But why, what's the point of it all?
Ah ha
Dig it, dig it!
Dig it now!
Can't see, can't speak, can't hear
A wise man draws closer to death
Just ask and I'll gladly stop
if that's allowed then we're allowed to laugh
The heart's voice is echoing around
Like a carnival of tears and hope
In this feisty, dark morning
Don't go
Don't cry
Say goodbye as you fling yesterday away
And strain your voice of courage
for the sake of learning to love yourself
Like a sleepless flock of sheep, the cry of the lost heart
Don't look back, our world has just begun
Don't be thinking lonely thoughts
Will you do it? won't you? It's alright to not
Crying out at unexpected disaster
I'll praise you with everything I have
And then I saw a dream that continues through worlds
and the angels descended
And then, at the center of an everlasting sky
I want to be free
1, 2 and 3, 4, 5. Get up, Stand up, free your soul
1, 2 and 3, 4, 5. Stand up and make some noise!
Oh-ho do it, do it
Oh-ho do it now
The heart's voice is echoing around
Like a carnival of tears and hope
In this feisty, dark morning
Swinging around
Keep on advancing
Say goodbye as you fling yesterday away, and strain your voice of courage
for the sake of learning to love yourself
Like a sleepless flock of sheep, the cry of the lost heart
Don't look back, our world has just begun
Ah-ha dig it, dig it
Ah-ha dig it, dig it up
Oh-ho do it, do it
Oh-ho do it now, do it now, do it now
In the bright blue sky, the hibiscus flower suddenly blooms in the summer morning
The time we'll meet again will come, when I told my dad that, he smiled sadly a little
You treasure and hug me, when I call out 'mum', when tears flowed from my eyes
You're surely going to be happy from now on, always hugging me
it's been embarassing up 'till now, to say the words out loud, but I'll always love you
Thank you for my life, thank you from the bottom of my heart
I want to properly convey these feelings
no matter how far apart we are, I'll always be thinking of you
and I'll always, always, always
Love you
It looks wonderful on you, Endo Shiori-sama
Really?
It doesn't feel too fitting
That's not true, it fits you perfectally
Speaking of it, I'm really nervous and restless
Next month
Reigetsu ni a kore wo kite shikyu ageru ka ttomoto
I feel like the person I see in the mirror is not the real me
Ah, that is surely the 'marriage blues'
Marriage blues? Me?
Hanayomesan wa youku naru mitai desu yo
Even though happiness is right in front of you
You think 'Is this really alright?', lose hope and become blue
You've been alone for the last 3 days haven't you
business trip
You're still saying good things about your parents
Isn't it amazing
With this you'll absolutely be happy
"Is it ok to be this happy?"
Then get anxious about it
That's right, that sounds about right
Sorry for saying something so selfish
Could I be left alone for a moment
Of course
Please think about your happiness
Since I was a kid
I've always been the obedient Shiori
I also loved my mum and dad
So, I always did as I was told
During school was the same
sitting was the same
It was the same about the person I was to marry
Watching a documentry on TV, made me think
To me,
I suddenly thought I could live freely
My heart's all over the place
I thought about running away too
But, I'm the good girl, Shiori-chan
During the wedding next month, I'll probably cry beautiful tears, I know that
I've arrived
This is amazing! You can even go to a parallel world
Hey, who are you, suddenly appearing here?
Shiori
What are you wearing?
It doesn't suit you at all
Please don't say such rude things
Who are you, suddenly appearing here?
Kanako! Kanako from the dance club. Your best friend, Kanako.
You know me right?
How am I meant to know, We've just met
Is your godfather
Who is this girl
It's true isn't it, you've lost your memories
Where did you come from, I'll call the staff
Wait right there
Were you born in the edo period? (1603-1868)
I get what's going on
The real you isn't like this
In your heart you're a far far more silly person, much more chatty and a glutton
I don't really know what you're saying
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Don't you remember, it's the song we were going to dance to in the competition
But, somehow, I felt something in my chest
See, inside your heart you still remember
I'm sure your body will move too
No way
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
What? Shiori-sama
Very
Nothings wrong, I was just so happy I started singing
Is that so? If you need anything else, just call
ok
Hurry up and go, I'm really busy
Tomorrow's the competition! We need to dance
You're so slow at understanding
See you
Wait, who are you?
I'll see you again, I've got other places to go
Wait
Shiori-sama?
Endo Shiori-sama?
Yes?
Sorry for intruding, this is the madame of the dress salon
You're different from the last person aren't you?
Correct, the usual madame has gotten a little sick
This is the temporary, singing madame
thank you
You're welcome
What are you here for?
Have you seen anything suspicious?
Yeah, someone just appeared out of nowhere
As we thought
I don't really understand it but she asked me to dance with her
As expected, so, what did you do? Did you dance together?
I didn't do anything, my parents dislike it.
They say dance is such a pointless thing
So, I dislike it too
Incredible, you've been excellently reborn!
Huh?
Even so, it's too soon to tell
She's still got the key to pass through worlds
Let's continue the plan
Um, what was that about?
Nothing, it's no big deal
Don't worry about any of that
You're just a bit bored
You look lovely in your dress, you'll definitely have a wonderful wedding
To your happiness, shall we go?
yes
What was that about?
Who was that girl?
Why did I, dance?
I won't let it bother me
Do you, do you, do you wanna dance
A musical would be good too
What!
Do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Look, you're putting it together, our dance
We'll definitely meet again
Hey, wait
Watanabe
What's up, did someone come?
The dance
I started to do the dance
No way
If a strong wind starts to blow
and the light starts to fade
Let's eat warming food together
Let's talk about it together and laugh
I wonder if there's a god out there or not
I don't really know, but with these hands
Slowly
There was hope
Onwards to the other side
Takada Reni-san
Yes
Sorry manager
Sorry, I'll be more careful
Thank you
Manager
What is it Kabayama?
About next weeks shift, on Tuesday and Thursday I usually go to the gym
It's fine, I'll do them
Thanks so much
I'll leave it to you
I'll do it
It's fine, I get along with the staff well
Takada, good luck with all your work
yes
Manager, is there something different about you today?
I just changed my makeup
It's cute
At the same time, they'd call be ugly and bully me
Since I was young, I thought so too
Because I had no friends and my parents were always busy I was alone
But love always wins
Huh?
Don't come so close
I'm Kanako, don't you remember?
I don't know you
I thought so
Shiori and Ayaka were the same too
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
What's this?
It kind of, feels warm
Doesn't it
Let's dance
No way
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
What?
No way
It's happening, this is real
If we gather everyone, something amazing will happen
Why did I dance like that?
Takada-san
I don't know my friends
I want to go meet my real self
No matter where
Don't cry
Don't lose
I'll believe in myself
Is this a dream?
Why is it so?
Can you see it?
Is it love?
Excuse me
Yes?
Where is this?
I don't know either, I got lost
You too?
Yeah, this strange person appeared
Was she called Kanako?
That's right
Me too
She had sparkling eyes but said unbelievable things right?
That's right, she was like a positive idiot
She said I didn't suit my wedding dress
You're getting married?
I'm Shiori
I'm Reni, I'm a nurse
I'm Ayaka, the acting club's director
And the 3 of us have all previously met Kanako
Didn't she say something weird, something about the past
Yeah she did, that we were all part of the same dance club in the past
Could it have been us?
"Tomorrow's the competition, we have to dance"
No way, something so silly
I don't know
But I thought, is this alright?
But she sung it right?
That dance song
She did
My heart seemed to remember it
Then my body started to move itself
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you
Do you wanna dance
That's good, everyone's gathered
Hey, you. Why have we all been brought here?
Where is this?
I didn't do anything, you guys chose to come here right?
I don't know where this is either
Anyway, I wanted to talk to you all now you're here
This goes shoot
and, shoot
I don't get it
Are you really an idiot?
But that's funny
It does sound like this girl came up with a story
It's fine if you don't believe it
It might be unbelievably weird
but would you just listen to my story?
What is it?
We are all from the same school's dance club
All second year
We became friends in first year, then formed the dance club
we watched loads of dance videos on youtube
We always practiced during breaks, after school, even at the weekend
To perform on that stage together
It's the greatest feeling
We thought that it was the most fun time in our lives
and then
and then?
we were killed in a traffic accident
eh?
Reni, Shiori, Ayaka and I died
Then before I realised it
you guys were reborn
huh?
When being reborn, the possibilites are infinite
Why's that? Because parallel worlds are infinite
but then, I tried searching for you
The luck of the gachapon
Even so, I really think this is fate
It's so odd, it's hard to believe it
but it's interesting
if it's all true, that's really crazy
You can't believe that
I don't believe it
I don't belive this, I'm just a good girl who listens to her parents
Just a normal, good girl
That's not true Shiori
You were the most obsessed with dancing
That song, you found it on youtube
Because I'm bad at English, everyone put it into katakana
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you remember?
It's like, when I see everyones faces, I remember a little
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
See, you knew that right?
I don't really know it, it came from within my chest
Do you, do you, do you, do you
do you wanna dance
You're doing it!
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you
Do you wanna dance
Oh! Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you
Do you wanna dance
Oh! Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you
Do you wanna dance
One, two
Come on out to the front
The real thing starts now
5, 6. 5, 6, 7 go
Hey! You lot back there, what are you doing? Come join the others
Don't stand apart
5, 6. 5, 6, 7 go
Ok, change the line
(Time?) is quick
Jump to the beat
Feel it in your toes
5, 6. 5, 6, 7 go
That concludes the first round
Please wait there for the results
Understood
Huh.. Ok!
Hey, what's going on here?
Looks like I messed up
we were supposed to go to the competition
Is this an audition?
What's this audition for?
I don't know
Hey, you four
yes?
I can't see your entry numbers
What entry numbers?
Ah!
What's this about?
Right then, I'll announce the results
put them on
Quickly
1, 4, 5, 8, 11, 13, 14, 17
That's all
Thanks for trying
Thank you very much
I'm the manager, yamagami
Before the final round,
The producer, chako will say a few words
I'm Chako
Our vision is to create a unique idol group never seen before
They'll start from their first show
and grow together with the fans
I want to see your confidence
I don't need it to be beautiful
Sing with everything, dance with everything
But
The guarantee for success is...
none
If you're not prepared, please leave
The last round will be an interview
Please show me what you've got
Then the interviews began
I hadn't thought of being an idol before
I don't know why I'm here, but I am
I'm sure the people who failed will feel fustrated
I don't want to lose, that feeling began to emerge
Let's dance
You want to dance right? The four of us
I wanna dance
Alright, let's have the next group
I'll ask a question, please answer individually
What are dreams to you?
To live more freely
To receive appeal and an applause
To have self confidence
For the four of us to dance
Also, to make everyone smile
One more question
Please tell me what 'Dance' means to you in one word
Freedom
A wave
Courage
Friendship
Thank you, that's the end of the questions
I'll now announce the results
numbers 3, 6, 9, 12, 15, 18, 19, 20, 21
All of you have passed, congratulations
We passed!?
Listen up, your groups name will be 'Heaven'
So from now, you will be members of Heaven
Let's do our best!
Do you wanna dance and hold my hand
Tell me baby I'm your lover man
Baby, do you wanna dance
Do you wanna dance under the moonlight
Hold me baby
Baby, do you wanna dance
Oh, do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you
Do you wanna dance
Oh, do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you
Do you wanna dance
Oh, do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you
Do you wanna dance
Oh, do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you
Do you wanna dance
Oh, do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you wanna dance
Do you, do you, do you, do you
Do you wanna dance
This is so fun! I want to dance with everyone forever
Full powered girl
I'll always love you with everything I have
I just wanted to tell you that
Do your best
ok
bye bye
I can't sop smiling
My heart won't stop dancing
so I start to move towards you
Run! Run! Run!
I've always seen you on the same train as me
I wonder when it began, when these feelings inside my heart became so big
Unable to ever start a conversation
I always pretended to talk with my friends
whilst watching you from the corner of my eye
I don't want to regret anymore now I've noticed these feelings
I don't want to lie to myself or run away from it
I'll gather up all my overflowing feelings and put them all into words
I can't stop smiling
My heart won't stop dancing
and so I start to move towards you
Run! Run! Run!
Right now I don't have the courage!
There aren't enough little chances
and so I start to move my body
Run! Run! Run!
nothing starts if you wait
I want to face you with all my strength
We were born on this same planet
We were born in the same period of time
words like chance are such simple words
disagreeing and accidentally distancing ourselves
just thinking of it hurts my chest
I want to get to know the real you, even now
however many years, however many decades, from now unto forever
because we only have one chance to live
I want to be honest when I'm with you
even so I still can't give you an answer
I can't even say the smallest of words
"I love you"
will those words alone change the world, will they?
I can't stop smiling
My heart won't stop dancing
and so I start to move towards you
and run! Run! Run!
Right now I don't have the courage!
There aren't enough little chances
and so I start to move my body
and run! Run! Run!
Dark weekend, come on Raideen!
No more laughing today
My power was cut
I'm on the verge of crying
Dark weekend, come on Raideen!
Where are the tickets to the promised land?
A sleepless doll, stripped of freedom
Cold and hungry nightmares
their fingers point to those who don't arrive
Wanting worship, more and more
I'm left wanting more
This timing is a curse
(the power has been cut)
screaming 'till my nose bleeds, is that supposed to happen?
Ruin is collapsing onto me
Dark weekend, come on raideen!
Poison comes from my mouth, burying into the mud
Left in silence with my weakness
Ripping open a door, shaken to the soul
I heard a serious voice
Hit me firmly
Selling your soul for victory won't bring joy
I heard the voice once again
Raideen echos
My soul is embedded into my heart
The beat awakens me
Abracadabra
Aarin
Standing before me, dazzling my eyes
I see a god of salvation
He has chosen me
He believes in me, let's move onwards
I won't miss out on my wish
counting on the pride of consuming the darkness
If I mourn, nothing new can be born
If I become wild, it'll be in vain
I recieved in gratitude
I live off giving back
I know, you know the agony of pain
If can I love, I can pray
Clear the way, Let's go!
Calm the pain
This world lives off negativity
Always take the chance to move ahead
Hold on, don't let go
Hey, come on. Hello Raideen
Firmly join together, we're invincible
Brace yourself and get ready. It's wonderful
I hate unfinished arguments
Being straightforward is best
A cruel merry go round
causes tears to spiral
Bury the flame of evil with a trial
Poison comes from my mouth, burying into the mud
Left in silence with my weakness, forever
Ripping open a door, shaken to the soul
I heard a serious voice
Hit me firmly
Selling your soul for victory won't bring joy
I heard the voice once again
Raideen echos
Thanks to your blessing, I won't give up
I'll pierce through the torn sky
My Soul is embedded into my heart
The sound of this beat has gained meaning
Abracadabra
Even through those twisting, difficult times
Like Noah's ark
We'll go towards the future
without wasting any time
I won't forget the places and people I met
Like Noah's ark
I embraced them
The shining weekend
AARGGH
It hurts!
that was funny wasn't it
yeah
the world of dreams is great
I feel like a kid again
is this really Ok
what?
Kanja-san's waiting for me
Tanaka-san's grandma
NOT COMPLETE
you're right
I can't give up on my acting club either
CHECK
what about my marriage?
I can't run away from it
I can't leave him to the kitchen
If we think about it
If we labelled that short lived dream we formed that day as 'A'
Then the future will be 'B'
If there's a god out there, please let 'A' and 'B' become the same
Combine them, draw a line between them
Then chip at them, break them
That's the conclusion I came to every time
Don't say that 'it's a mistake' that you managed to find me
Even if we're reborn, and can still understand
Make me remember once more
Watch as we reach our limit
Just don't forget us, always
Always
Let the distance between you and I be 'C' and 'D'
Like equal, parallel lines
Even now you can still dance along to that eight beat song
that'll bring us closer together
Write it down, erase it
break the pencil lead
Still, I can't give an answer
Tear up the answer sheet
Even so, I'll still solve it
The dream I saw with you
Even if we're reborn, and can still understand
Make me remember once more
Watch as we reach our limit
Just don't forget us
The entirety of the your dancing figure
is laughing, sending the same message as always
From the moment I remember being reborn
to the future, let's get along
Even if we're reborn, and can still understand
Make me remember once more
Watch as we reach our limit
Just don't forget us
Always
Hey, what was your name again?
Where did we meet again?
When was it again?
What were we doing again?
What was your face like again?
What was your voice like again?
What kind of person where you again?
Where was your favourite place again?
I don't want to forget
Let's meet again tomorrow
Let's make it a promise
Even if we're reborn
I don't want to change
I'll always find you again
Bye bye
Don't forget me